<?xml version='1.0' encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="DeiNewsCNNRipoff.xsl"?>
<!-- Generated automatically. Don't change it. -->
<cnn_news_list>
    <news_us>
        <news_item>
            <title>Body found believed to be that of actress Misty Upham - CNN.com</title>
            <date>2014-10-16T21:51:24Z</date>
            <author>Todd Leopold and Brandon Griggs, CNN</author>
            <highlights>NEW: Police say a purse containing Upham's ID was found with the body Actress was last seen October 5 and reported missing the next day Upham appeared in "August: Osage County" and "Frozen River"</highlights>
            <text>(CNN) -- The body of "August: Osage County" actress Misty Upham is believed to have been found along a river in suburban Seattle, police said Thursday. The body was found by a member of Upham's family during a search for the actress, according to police in Auburn, Washington. It was found at the bottom of a steep embankment near the White River. The body has not been officially identified, but a purse containing Upham's ID was found with the remains, police said. Upham, 32, was last seen October 5 walking from her sister's apartment in Muckleshoot, Washington, according to a statement sent to media outlets by her father, Charles Upham. She was reported missing the following day. Actress' disappearance baffles family Her father said she has bipolar disorder and bouts of depression and anxiety, but didn't think she was suicidal. "The truth is Misty is not stressed over money or career. Her career is going great," he wrote Sunday. "As her father I do not fear she committed suicide. I feel that she has been hurt by accident or someone has put her in harms way." Upham had small roles in "Django Unchained" and "August: Osage County," and was nominated for an Independent Spirit Award for her performance in 2008's "Frozen River." She's also had roles in the TV series "Big Love" and the TV movie "Skinwalkers." She was currently shooting a film called "Crawlspace," according to the Internet Movie Database. CNN's Cheri Mossburg and Lorenza Brascia also contributed to this story. Loading weather data ...</text>
            <url>http://www.cnn.com/2014/10/16/showbiz/celebrity-news-gossip/misty-upham-missing/index.html?hpt=us_c1</url>
            <videos>
                <video>http://ht.cdn.turner.com/cnn/big/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo.smil</video>
                <video>http://cnnios-f.akamaihd.net/i/cnn/big/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_ios_,150,440,650,1240,.mp4.csmil/master.m3u8?__b__=650</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_561702_768x432_1300k.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_ios_150.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_640x360_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_cnn_iphone_cell.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_ios_audio.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_561702_640x360_900k.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo.ipad.qtref.mov</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_561702_1280x720_3500k.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_640x360_900k.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_cnn_iphone_wifi_hi.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_ios_1240.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_ios_440.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo.qtref.mov</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_320x180_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_ios_650.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_512x288_550k.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_384x216_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_561702_896x504_1850k.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_561702_512x288_550k.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_416x234_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_768x432_1300k.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_ios_3000.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_1280x720_3500k.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_ios_840.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_576x324_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_896x504_1850k.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_1280x720.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_768x432.mp4</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_256x144_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/us/2014/10/16/wa-vosil-possible-body-found-misty-upham.komo_youtube_640x360.flv</video>
            </videos>
        </news_item>
    </news_us>
    <news_africa>
        <news_item>
            <title>Ebola fears crippling Africa's safari industry - CNN.com</title>
            <date>2014-10-17T07:37:41Z</date>
            <author>Karla Cripps, CNN</author>
            <highlights>Safari operators report cancellations, huge drop in bookings due to Ebloa fears Geographical misconceptions are leading many travelers to avoid Africa completely Tour operator: "Many people still look at Africa as a homogeneous country and not as the second largest continent"</highlights>
            <text>(CNN) -- With travel to Africa poised to hit all-time highs in 2014, a drop-off in travel bookings was the last thing the continent's lucrative safari industry thought it would be facing going into 2015. But despite the fact that the main safari destinations in southern and eastern Africa are thousands of kilometers from the Ebola-stricken countries of the west, industry leaders say fears of the disease are keeping tourists away. A survey based on feedback from more than 500 safari operators conducted by African booking company Safaribookings.com found that as of late September, more than half reported a 20 to 70% decline in bookings. "Numerous safari tour operators report to us that clients view Africa as a single country when it comes to risk assessment," Wouter Vergeer, Safaribookings.com founder, tells CNN. Vergeer says the impact is most noticeable in East Africa, home to safari hotspots such as Kenya's Masai Mara and Tanzania's Serengeti -- places located nearly 5,000 kilometers from the West Africa Ebola outbreak area. "Most people don't realize how vast Africa is and that East and southern Africa are just as far from the outbreak area as Europe or South America," says Vergeer. "All safari countries have enacted strict precautionary measures and as there currently are no Ebola cases the risk of infection is effectively zero." Convincing clients they'll be safe Jake McCormick, a safari specialist with Shadows of Africa, says the Ebola outbreak has caused a 70% decrease in inquiries at his company, which offers tours in Tanzania, Kenya, Rwanda and Zanzibar. "We are still working to try to convince clients they are safe from this disease, but until we see the outbreak come under control my feeling is that it will be a while until things return to normal," he says. Joao Oliveira, founder of It Started in Africa, which organizes safaris and Kilimanjaro treks in Tanzania and Kenya, tells a similar story. "We did not have any cancellations but we had much fewer bookings," he says. "The reason I believe there have been no cancellations is because the clients who have already paid -- safaris are usually booked several months in advance and a down payment is required -- do their own research and find out that the Ebola countries are more than 5,000 kilometers away from Tanzania or Kenya. "As for the reduction in bookings, I believe it is because those who are planning their vacations are now not even considering going to Africa because of Ebola." Oliveira says 2014 was on track to be his company's most profitable year to date. Then, as news of the Ebloa crisis spread, panic set in. "In July, we projected that August would be our best month ever and then the panic started and August was the worst month of the last two years. September was the same." He says October looks like it's improving slightly but it's difficult to tell at this point. "It does not make sense," he adds. "You would not cancel your vacation in Paris because there are conflicts in the Middle East or in Ukraine. If something nasty was happening in Alaska, you'd still go to New York." MORE: 'Fear-bola' hits epidemic proportions 'Africa is seen as a country' Brett Thomson, managing director of Sun Safaris, says that in addition to traveler queries being down 50 to 70%, new bookings compared with last October are also down about 50%. "Over the past month we have had numerous clients replying that they will be in touch after all the health scares are over," says Thomson. "Even if we explain how far southern Africa is from West Africa, it does not change their mind. Africa is seen as a country and hardly ever as a continent." Daniel Njamwea, managing director of safari travel booking company Lilac Adventures, agrees that it's been difficult trying to convince clients how far East Africa is from West Africa -- especially Kenya. "This morning I was dealing with clients over Skype who are coming on October 25 and are worried since they read in the news that there is a woman who died at Jomo Kenyatta airport last weekend and feared that she had Ebola," says Njamwea. "It was hard to convince them that she tested negative for Ebola. I had to refer them to Ministry of Health website to read more details." The other big problem, say those in the industry, is a lack of knowledge of how Ebola is contracted. "Although the Ebola virus is not airborne at this time and can only be caught through coming in contact with the bodily fluids of an infected person, and is currently limited to destinations in West Africa, we have recently experienced a small number of clients deferring their holiday plans to the rest of the continent," says Charlie Bateson, product director of high end travel company Abercrombie &amp; Kent. "We remain in constant contact with the FCO, WHO and with tourist boards and our supplier partners across the world. "Our tour consultants are given the latest news on developments and have the ability to specifically advise clients on how the virus is transmitted so that they are able to allay clients fears." Meanwhile, Rose Hipwood of the Luxury Safari Company says the top end of Africa's safari market hasn't been hit as hard by Ebola fears "since many of those clients are international travelers and can look at the situation sensibly." "Some clients have indeed decided not to book safaris this year after inquiring -- but sadly in this industry we get a lot of time wasters and I believe those people would have found another reason not to book if not Ebola, although families are always more protective of their little ones," says Hipwood. Africa tourism was poised for growth Though no figures have been released on the overall impact Ebola has had on African tourism, in the first half of 2014 the industry had been experiencing impressive growth rates. According to the World Tourism Organization's 2014 global travel report, Africa was due to see 4 to 6% tourism growth this year. In 2013, the continent saw international arrivals increase 5% over 2012, the equivalent of 3 million more tourists, to reach 56 million. "This year is (now) written off already," says Njamwea, of Lilac Adventures. "By this time hotels should be issuing stop sales for the Christmas period, but I have seen none, meaning they still have availability. "Though this could have been due to other factors like cancellations of direct charter flights from Europe due to security risks, Ebola has too played a great part." London-based James Strawson tells CNN he'd been considering a trip to Gambia in late November until the Ebola crisis erupted. "I wanted to go away for some winter sunshine," he says. "I've been to Gambia previously and it's a good time zone, easy to get to and quite nice and warm." Strawson, 26, said media "hysteria" related to Ebola changed his mind. "I just looked at the headlines and thought, it looks bad now, who knows what it will look like in a few weeks?" Strawson, who works in finance, says he's not completely ruled out an Africa trip and is now planning a vacation in Zanzibar. 'World-class epidemiological detective work' Since the outbreak started in March, about 9,000 Ebola cases and 4,493 deaths have been reported, mostly in Guinea, Liberia and Sierra Leone, according to the World Health Organization (WHO). More than half of the deaths have been in Liberia. And the numbers are expected to skyrocket. There could be up to 10,000 new Ebola cases per week in the three hardest-hit nations by the end of the year, the WHO said. It warned that things will get worse before they get better. In August, WHO issued a warning saying Kenya had a high risk of experiencing an Ebola outbreak, but as yet the country hasn't seen a single case. The WHO says it's due to declare the end of the Ebola outbreak in Senegal and Nigeria on Friday and Monday, respectively. "In a piece of world-class epidemiological detective work, all confirmed cases in Nigeria were eventually linked back to the Liberian air traveler who introduced the virus into the country on July 20," said WHO in a statement. MORE: Liberia has shortage of body bags, supplies to fight Ebola outbreak Precautionary measures in eastern and southern African countries fighting to keep Ebola from entering their borders vary, with some countries banning travelers who have visited affected countries, while others have adopted strict border screening measures. Botswana, for instance, has reportedly suspended entry for travelers who have visited Liberia, Guinea, Nigeria and Sierra Leone in the last 30 days. In Tanzania, all major border posts have mandatory health screening in place, including all international airports. South Africa refuses to admit foreign citizens arriving from Ebola-affected countries in West Africa, while South African citizens will be allowed to re-enter, but only after being subject to strict screening. The Africa Travel Association (ATA), a global trade association that promotes travel and tourism to Africa, released a statement to CNN. "According to the WHO, the most severely affected countries are Guinea, Liberia and Sierra Leone, however, the Africa tourism industry has felt stark repercussions across the continent through economic losses, canceled flights and bookings, closed borders and negative perceptions," it said. "These impacts reach far beyond the borders of those affected countries. ATA urges the travel industry and traveling public to remain cautious, however, to acknowledge the immense size of the continent and to continue to travel to the vast majority of the countries that remain safe." MORE: Questions after woman being monitored for Ebola flies commercially  Loading weather data ...</text>
            <url>http://www.cnn.com/2014/10/17/travel/africa-safaris-ebola/index.html?hpt=iaf_t2</url>
            <photos>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017101730-safari-ebola-leopard-botswana-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017102435-safari-ebola-elephant-tanzania-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017101200-safari-ebola-hippo-kruger-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017102400-safari-ebola-giraffes-botswana-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017100815-safari-ebola-tourist-okavango-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017101034-safari-ebola-cubs-edeni-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017130801-safari-ebola-kenya-airport-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
            </photos>
        </news_item>
        <news_item>
            <title>Ebola outbreak: Liberia has shortage of body bags - CNN.com</title>
            <date>2014-10-16T08:12:36Z</date>
            <author>Faith Karimi, CNN</author>
            <highlights>Ebola has killed at least 4,493 people, mostly in Guinea, Liberia and Sierra Leone, WHO says Liberia is short of supplies needed to fight the virus Items lacking include protective suits, gloves and goggles The grim inventory highlights how ill-equipped the nation is to fight Ebola</highlights>
            <text>(CNN) -- As the world reels from its worst Ebola outbreak, the nation hardest hit is declaring a shortage of body bags, which are crucial to preventing the spread of the deadly virus. Liberia, one of three countries most affected by the outbreak, said it has 4,900 body bags nationwide. It needs 85,000 more in the next six months, the Health Ministry said in a statement. A grim inventory of supplies shows body bags were not the only items lacking. Liberia is also experiencing a shortage of other supplies needed to fight the virus, including protective suits, face masks, gloves and goggles. Liberia said it needs 2.4 million boxes of gloves in the next six months, but it has only 18,000 boxes. Each box has 100 pairs. It also needs about 1.2 million hooded overalls within the same time frame, but it has only 165,000. The numbers are the latest setback in Liberia's fight against Ebola, which has killed at least 2,458 people in the nation. This week, health workers in the nation went on strike to demand higher pay, leaving some clinics unattended. Since the outbreak started in March, about 9,000 Ebola cases and 4,493 deaths have been reported, mostly in Guinea, Liberia and Sierra Leone, according to the World Health Organization. More than half of the deaths have been in Liberia. And the numbers are expected to skyrocket. There could be up to 10,000 new Ebola cases per week in the three hardest-hit nations by the end of the year, the World Health Organization said. It warned that things will get worse before they get better. Liberia has some supplies arriving in the next week, but it says they are still insufficient. Items scheduled to arrive don't include body bags. In addition to the three nations, a handful of Ebola cases have also been reported in Senegal, Nigeria, Spain and the United States.  Loading weather data ...</text>
            <url>http://www.cnn.com/2014/10/16/world/africa/ebola-liberia-overwhelmed/index.html?hpt=iaf_c1</url>
            <videos>
                <video>http://ht.cdn.turner.com/cnn/big/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn.smil</video>
                <video>http://cnnios-f.akamaihd.net/i/cnn/big/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_ios_,150,440,650,1240,.mp4.csmil/master.m3u8?__b__=650</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_223732_768x432_1300k.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_ios_150.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_640x360_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_cnn_iphone_cell.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_ios_audio.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_223732_640x360_900k.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn.ipad.qtref.mov</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_223732_1280x720_3500k.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_640x360_900k.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_ios_1240.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_cnn_iphone_wifi_hi.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_ios_440.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_320x180_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn.qtref.mov</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_ios_650.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_512x288_550k.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_384x216_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_223732_896x504_1850k.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_416x234_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_223732_512x288_550k.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_768x432_1300k.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_ios_3000.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_1280x720_3500k.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_ios_840.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_576x324_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_896x504_1850k.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_1280x720.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_768x432.mp4</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_256x144_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/health/2014/10/09/this-is-the-messy-truth-about-ebola-miguel-marquez-graphic-orig.cnn_youtube_640x360.flv</video>
            </videos>
        </news_item>
    </news_africa>
    <news_asia>
        <news_item>
            <title>Inside China's gateway to North Korea - CNN.com</title>
            <date>2014-10-17T05:17:50Z</date>
            <author>David McKenzie, CNN</author>
            <highlights>Dandong is a thriving Chinese border town within throwing distance of North Korea Much trade -- legal and illegal -- is done between the two countries One smuggler talks to CNN about the business he does with N. Korean soldiers But he claims Dandong is crawling with North Korean spies</highlights>
            <text>Dandong, China (CNN) -- The sun is rising over the Yalu River and North Korea. Revolutionary music pumped through loudspeakers wafts over to China. Back across the river, work groups can be seen stirring for a day's toil in the fields. Over here in China, a tourist tout is trying to sell us North Korean currency. "Good price!" he shouts. This is daily life in Dandong, China -- a thriving border town within throwing distance of the Hermit Kingdom. Tourists often do just that when they go right up to the fence that separates the two countries and leave cigarettes, old watches and other goodies for the North Korean border guards. Signs all along the border warn against throwing goods over the fence, as if it's some kind of zoo. And, in a way, that's what it has become. Chinese tourists now flock to Dandong -- which lies along China's western border with the Democratic People's Republic of Korea -- to ogle at their unfortunate neighbors. Some pay a few RMB to borrow binoculars to peer across the river, while the more adventurous take speedboats and pleasure cruises out on the river, which acts a natural barrier between the two neighbors. "Go inside North Korea!" a sign for one local boat company proclaims. Perhaps the Chinese come to marvel at how far they have come. With decades of breakneck growth, Communist China has become a testament to capitalism and urban living. North Korea, which also describes itself as a socialist state, is still sealed and secretive -- almost. Lifeline Dandong is the lifeline, say critics, of the autocratic regime led by Kim Jong Un. Whole neighborhoods in the back streets of the city are lined with trading shops quietly run by North Korean officials. China is North Korea's largest trading partner by a long way, and despite Beijing's official displeasure with the DPRK's pursuit of nuclear weapons, this trade continues to grow. China has rebuffed any attempts to strengthen economic sanctions further against Pyongyang. READ: Why has North Korea decided to talk now? Up to 70% of all China trade with North Korea runs through Dandong, according to South Korea's Yonhap news agency, and it takes the form of both legal trade and illegal smuggling. We meet "Chen," a smuggler who makes a midnight run across the Yalu several times a month to trade with North Korean soldiers. "In China we don't lack food, we don't lack things," he says. "People can eat and have clothes on their backs, but not over there, even the North Korean soldiers have nothing." Despite North Korean propaganda that paints a picture of their military as an elite fighting force, Chen says the soldiers are desperate for basic food such as bread and rice. They don't have money so they barter with scrap metals, old pots and even ginseng. But Chen says he can never trade with ordinary North Koreans, the soldiers wouldn't allow it. North Korean spies We can't use Chen's real name, he claims that Dandong is crawling with North Korean spies. "Don't say anything sensitive around the North Korean waitresses," he whispers to us. "They speak Korean and English." And you can find them all across Dandong in North Korean themed restaurants, karaoke bars, and musical review shows. We head to one of the more famous ones along the river. If refugees are caught trying to escape from North Korea, they are shot, but in restaurants like this gaudy two-story tourist trap, North Koreans are allowed to work in China on special three-year permits. They are often the children of mid-level Korean Workers' Party loyalists and their movements and earnings are tightly controlled. And as the four-piece all-female North Korean band plays to the Chinese tourists drinking North Korean beer, I think how perfectly it sums up this city: extremely bizarre and perhaps a little tragic. READ: Another N. Korean overture as questions remain about Kim  Loading weather data ...</text>
            <url>http://www.cnn.com/2014/10/17/world/asia/china-dandong-north-korea-mckenzie/index.html?hpt=ias_t2</url>
            <photos>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017125855-dandong-1-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017130143-dandong-3-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017125729-dandong-2-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141017130242-dandong-4-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
            </photos>
            <videos>
                <video>http://ht.cdn.turner.com/cnn/big/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn.smil</video>
                <video>http://cnnios-f.akamaihd.net/i/cnn/big/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_ios_,150,440,650,1240,.mp4.csmil/master.m3u8?__b__=650</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_561814_768x432_1300k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_640x360_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_ios_150.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_cnn_iphone_cell.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_ios_audio.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_561814_640x360_900k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn.ipad.qtref.mov</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_561814_1280x720_3500k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_640x360_900k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_ios_1240.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_cnn_iphone_wifi_hi.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_ios_440.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_320x180_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn.qtref.mov</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_ios_650.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_512x288_550k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_384x216_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_561814_896x504_1850k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_416x234_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_561814_512x288_550k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_768x432_1300k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_ios_3000.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_1280x720_3500k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_ios_840.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_576x324_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_896x504_1850k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_1280x720.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_768x432.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_256x144_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/pkg-mckenzie-north-korea-lifeline.cnn_youtube_640x360.flv</video>
            </videos>
        </news_item>
        <news_item>
            <title>16 dead in vent grate collapse at South Korea concert - CNN.com</title>
            <date>2014-10-17T12:15:55Z</date>
            <author>CNN Staff</author>
            <highlights></highlights>
            <text>(CNN) -- At least 16 people died Friday when a grate over a ventilation shaft collapsed at an outdoor concert in Seongnam, South Korea, an official with the National Emergency Management Agency told CNN. About two dozen people fell some 10 meters (33 feet), according to the official, who declined to be identified because he is not authorized to speak to the media. The accident occurred during an outdoor concert at a multipurpose venue called Pangyo Techo Valley, according to South Korea's Yonhap news agency. CNN's K.J. Kwon contributed to this report. Loading weather data ...</text>
            <url>http://www.cnn.com/2014/10/17/world/asia/south-korea-concert-accident/index.html?hpt=ias_c1</url>
            <videos>
                <video>http://ht.cdn.turner.com/cnn/big/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn.smil</video>
                <video>http://cnnios-f.akamaihd.net/i/cnn/big/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_ios_,150,440,650,1240,.mp4.csmil/master.m3u8?__b__=650</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_140752_768x432_1300k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_640x360_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_ios_150.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_cnn_iphone_cell.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_ios_audio.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_140752_640x360_900k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn.ipad.qtref.mov</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_140752_1280x720_3500k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_640x360_900k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_ios_1240.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_cnn_iphone_wifi_hi.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_ios_440.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_320x180_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn.qtref.mov</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_ios_650.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_512x288_550k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_384x216_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_140752_896x504_1850k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_416x234_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_140752_512x288_550k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_768x432_1300k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_ios_3000.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_1280x720_3500k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_ios_840.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_576x324_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_896x504_1850k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_1280x720.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_768x432.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_256x144_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/17/cnni-south-korea-stage-collapse.cnn_youtube_640x360.flv</video>
            </videos>
        </news_item>
    </news_asia>
    <news_europe>
        <news_item>
            <title>U.S. tourist gets trapped in London bookstore - CNN.com</title>
            <date>2014-10-17T11:29:35Z</date>
            <author>Barry Neild, CNN</author>
            <highlights>Texan David Willis wandered into London book store to use free WiFi Willis made phone calls after realizing he was locked in, but no one initially came to his aid He was released after three hours when his social media posts were spotted</highlights>
            <text>(CNN) -- There's nothing like getting stuck into a good book -- but getting stuck in a good book store is a different matter. Just ask David Willis, a tourist from Texas who was inadvertently locked inside a London retailer for several hours, after strolling in minutes before the store was closing. Willis, from Dallas, entered the Waterstones store near London's Trafalgar Square on Thursday evening to use the store's WiFi. "I walked into the store about five minutes before 9 p.m.," he told the UK's ITV television network. "I walked in right past employees and I needed to use the internet... I peeked up on the second floor and saw there were chairs and a table up there so I walked up there and was using the internet for 10 or 15 minutes and all the lights were on upstairs. "I get ready to leave and I walk down and it's completely dark and the doors were locked." Willis said despite setting an alarm off by trying to open the doors and speaking to a security guard and police via telephone, no one came to his aid. After several hours of waiting, he took to social media to broadcast his plight, posting on Twitter and Instagram. This is me locked inside a waterstones bookstore in London. I was upstairs for 15 minutes and came... http://t.co/EefA1antuG Hi @Waterstones I've been locked inside of your Trafalgar Square bookstore for 2 hours now. Please let me out. That did the trick. As his messages were retweeted thousands of times, a Waterstones employee spotted them and secured his release. The bookstore posted its own Twitter message shortly afterward, announcing: "We're pleased to announce that @DWill_ is a free man once more. Thanks for your concern and tweets!" We're pleased to announce that @DWill_ is a free man once more. Thanks for your concern and tweets! After three hours in captivity, Willis followed that with his own Twitter declaration: "I'm free". Speaking the morning after his ordeal, Willis told ITV: "I'm very tired, I did not sleep very much last night but it feels good to be free." I'm free READ MORE: The world's coolest bookstores  Loading weather data ...</text>
            <url>http://www.cnn.com/2014/10/17/travel/tourist-trapped-in-bookstore/index.html?hpt=ieu_t2</url>
            <photos>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140722113109-coolest-bookstores-10-library-el-ateneo-circular-roof-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140722120017-coolest-bookstores-14-shakespeare-entry-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140722111302-coolest-bookstores-8-last-bookstore-books-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140723102222-coolest-bookstores-lello-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140722104231-coolest-bookstore-2-assouline-white-wall-vertical-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140722104911-coolest-bookstore-3-boekhandel-archy-ceiling-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130828134135-nanjing-book-shop-15-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140724003230-coolest-bookstores-john-k-king-horizontal-gallery.jpeg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140723102104-coolest-bookstores-books-for-cooks-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140723191937-coolest-bookstores---powells-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140722110607-coolest-bookstores-6-parnassus-glass-books-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140724095832-coolest-bookstores-mexico-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140723045100-coolest-bookstores-vertical-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140723103514-coolest-bookstores-1200-bookshop-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140723101623-coolest-bookstores-foyles-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140722110840-coolest-bookstores-7-strand-red-tent-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140724000141-coolest-bookstores-eslite-dunnan-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
            </photos>
        </news_item>
        <news_item>
            <title>London terror suspect: 'Terrorist' describes me - CNN.com</title>
            <date>2014-10-16T18:52:09Z</date>
            <author>Nick Thompson and Laura Smith-Spark, CNN</author>
            <highlights>A British man charged with planning an attack said he had been to Syria, court hears Defendant Erol Incedal had documents on how to build a bomb, prosecution says Incedal denies two charges; a second defendant has admitted to one charge Police say Incedal had the address of a property belonging to former UK PM Tony Blair</highlights>
            <text>London (CNN) -- A British man charged with planning either a "Mumbai-style" terror attack or an attack on a prominent person said in secret recordings that he had been to Syria and reveled in the idea of being labeled a terrorist, a court in London heard Thursday. Erol Incedal, 26, is accused of preparing terrorist acts with the intention of committing terrorism, and of having documents on how to build a bomb. He denies the charges against him. Police first detained Incedal, a British citizen of Turkish descent, over a traffic violation in London in September 2013. During a search of his car, they found a piece of paper with the address of a property tied to former British Prime Minister Tony Blair written on it. Police planted a secret listening device in Incedal's E-Class Mercedes before releasing him. The recordings have been revealed this week at Incedal's trial, which will be partially held in secret. While the judge has allowed some reporting of its opening phases, journalists and members of the public will be barred from observing other parts of the trial. The prosecution says the recordings from inside Incedal's car give "a flavor" of the law student's frame of mind in the weeks before he was arrested again in October of last year and formally charged. In one clip, Incedal and his associate Mounir Rarmoul-Bouhadjar claim to have been in Syria. "In Syria, the weather was ...," Rarmoul-Bouhadjar says, before Incedal interjects with, "Wallahi, it was like minus-20 degrees because we were on a mountain!" "Another word, 'terrorist.' That's a great word, Mounir. There's never been a greater word than that to describe us," Incedal tells Rarmoul-Bouhadjar in another clip. The jury also heard recordings of Incedal and Rarmoul-Bouhadjar purportedly using code words in a discussion about buying a gun. Incedal told his partner: "Update me at every stage and just say 'yeah the sausage is nice, there's enough sauce in it.' " "What's the sausage?" Rarmoul-Bouhadjar asks. Incedal replies: "Bullets. If there's not enough sauce in it, you'll have to make that decision if we're gonna take it or not. If it's less than five, it's not worth it." In another clip, the pair appear to be discussing the quality of their potential purchase. "It is only about a grand, so I don't think it is going to be a great quality," says Incedal. Rarmoul-Bouhadjar asks, "It fires?" Incedal replies: "Mmm ... it's not a replica." In another recording, Rarmoul-Bouhadjar appears to suggest to Incedal that he should leave his wife. "I think you should separate," he tells Incedal. "She has mentally become unstable." "Do you know what I'm worried about now? She knows some of our secrets," Incedal replies. "She don't know much but she knows I was, like, in trouble. ... I'm not saying it's going to happen, but she might just chat s**t." Police finally decided to swoop in on October 13, 2013. Specialist firearms officers stopped the pair in east London and shot out the tires of Incedal's car to prevent an escape. They arrested both men and seized several iPhones and other mobile phones from the car, according to prosecutors. Prosecutors say Incedal's iPhone had a number of images on it, including an image of a YouTube page for a song called "O Islamic State" and an image of a page of titles by Anwar al-Awlaki, the radical U.S.-born cleric who was killed by an American drone strike in late September 2011 in Yemen. Both men's iPhones concealed an SD card between the phone and the phone's protective case. Both SD cards contained three identical files, including a "Car Bomb Recognition Guide" and a "bomb making" Word document, parts of which were considered "viable" but also incomplete, the court heard. Incedal and Rarmoul-Bouhadjar communicated via email and Skype, using code words and aliases to refer to the words "Kalashnikov" and "Mumbai-style," the prosecution said. More than 160 people were killed in November 2008 when 10 Pakistani gunmen associated with the terror group Lashkar-e-Tayyiba stormed buildings in Mumbai, India. Rarmoul-Bouhadjar has already pleaded guilty to one count of possessing a document that could be used in a terror attack. Officers searching Incedal's south London home also found a document on top of a wardrobe referring to a "Plan A" that appeared to be a checklist for an operation involving "three to four workers," "two tennis rackets," "one months' surveillance," and renting a flat nearby, Prosecutor Richard Whittam said. Incedal's wife, Kadeejah Baluch, was home at the time with Incedal's three children and another child. Police also searched a second address in west London that Incedal had failed to disclose to police at the time of his arrest. That search turned up a laptop with Incedal's DNA all over it and several Nicolas Cage DVDs, among other things, the court heard. It is unclear when the alleged terror plots were to be carried out. But during an argument with his wife that was captured by the police listening device inside his car, Incedal says: "I'm never going to be around for very long anyway ... at least my last few months of life, I'll live with peace of mind." The trial continues at the Old Bailey Central Criminal Court. CNN's Atika Shubert contributed to this report. Loading weather data ...</text>
            <url>http://www.cnn.com/2014/10/16/world/europe/uk-erol-incedal-terror-trial/index.html?hpt=ieu_c1</url>
            <videos>
                <video>http://ht.cdn.turner.com/cnn/big/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn.smil</video>
                <video>http://cnnios-f.akamaihd.net/i/cnn/big/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_ios_,150,440,650,1240,.mp4.csmil/master.m3u8?__b__=650</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_201542_768x432_1300k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_ios_150.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_640x360_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_cnn_iphone_cell.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_ios_audio.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_201542_640x360_900k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn.ipad.qtref.mov</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_201542_1280x720_3500k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_640x360_900k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_cnn_iphone_wifi_hi.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_ios_1240.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_ios_440.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_320x180_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn.qtref.mov</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_ios_650.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_512x288_550k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_384x216_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_201542_896x504_1850k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_201542_512x288_550k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_416x234_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_768x432_1300k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_ios_3000.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_ios_840.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_1280x720_3500k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_576x324_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_896x504_1850k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_1280x720.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_768x432.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_256x144_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/14/lok-shubert-uk-london-terror-trial.cnn_youtube_640x360.flv</video>
            </videos>
        </news_item>
    </news_europe>
    <news_latinamerica>
        <news_item>
            <title>The 10 best emerging market start up cities - CNN.com</title>
            <date>2014-10-13T11:04:45Z</date>
            <author>Peter Shadbolt, for CNN</author>
            <highlights>The internet means that a good business idea can germinate anywhere From Nairobi to Lagos and Tel Aviv to Lima, new cities are hosting the world's best startups A lack of basic infrastructure can be turned to advantage in regions like sub-Saharan Africa</highlights>
            <text>Editor's note: Virtual Think Tank is a digital series focusing on the emerging markets, covering their startups, the power of the middle classes on their economies and the macro environment. (CNN) -- It's no longer necessary to launch your startup in Silicon Valley -- thanks to the internet, you can do it anywhere. Cities that were once business backwaters have emerged as formidable contenders in the new economy, in many cases leveraging the very things that once disadvantaged them. A lack of infrastructure in places like Nairobi or Lagos, for instance -- once places where it took years to get a fixed line -- have skipped that generation of technology entirely and now offer tantalizing potential for a range of mobile services. "They are not held back by infrastructure issues and they've got nothing to lose by being in the startup space," said Simon Squibb, CEO of Hong Kong-based Nest Investment. "There's a whole opportunity around e-commerce or ed-tech." Without basic access to schools and banks, for example, sub-Saharan Africa has been at the cutting edge of ed-tech developments and mobile financial services. "They get forced into creative solutions and technology can often end up being that creative solution," Squibb said. "They end up being these pockets of activity partly by the need to create the infrastructure that was never built." Even so, those cities that will have the edge in the new technology race often have several fundamentals in place: a functioning education system, the rule of law and access to capital. "For me, Hong Kong still wins out," Squibb said. "Ultimately, liveability is a key a ingredient. You always need to import talent no matter where you are so having a great city for your core team definitely helps." Click through the gallery above to find out which emerging market cities, according to Squibb, are the best places to launch and nurture a startup. Read this: The 10 hottest startups in Asia right now Read this: How to raise cash through Facebook likes  Loading weather data ...</text>
            <url>http://www.cnn.com/2014/10/13/tech/10-best-emerging-market-start-up-cities/index.html?hpt=ila_t2</url>
            <photos>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141008145631-squibb-ho-chi-minh-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130712125903-ihub-martha-chumo-overview-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141008145612-squibb-bangalore-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141008145619-squibb-santiago-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130812120146-africa-tech-tablet-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141008145605-squibb-manila-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/130320170238-cc-hub-rooftop-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141008145644-squibb-lima-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141008132055-squibb-hk-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141008155732-squibb-telaviv-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
            </photos>
        </news_item>
        <news_item>
            <title>Hurricane Gonzalo sets its sights on Bermuda - CNN.com</title>
            <date>2014-10-17T09:15:14Z</date>
            <author>Ed Payne, CNN</author>
            <highlights>Hurricane Gonzalo is churning through the North Atlantic toward Bermuda Wind speeds are hitting 130 mph Bermuda is prepared, says the premier</highlights>
            <text>(CNN) -- Bermuda says it's ready. Now it awaits the arrival of Hurricane Gonzalo. The eye of the powerful Category 3 storm with its 130 mph winds and higher gusts is expected to pass near the British territory Friday evening, according to the National Hurricane Center in Miami. "Bermuda we are prepared," said island Premier Michael Dunkley. "Well rehearsed plans for most contingencies are enacted, and as we hope for the best, we are prepared for the worst." Ahead of the storm, Bermuda closed schools, shut down bus and ferry service, and opened up shelters. Hurricane conditions are expected to reach Bermuda on Friday afternoon, according to forecasters, with tropical storm conditions beginning later this morning. Bda thanks for the early prep for the storm and for watching our neighbors and seniors. Hunker down and be safe. God bless. Gonzalo is expected to deliver a power storm surge and significant coastal flooding. Rainfall amounts could hit 6 inches. It will slowly weaken as it approaches the island. 2014 Atlantic Hurricane Season facts Bermuda is no stranger to hurricanes, and has weathered a storm or two before. "We will come through this and once this serious storm has passed it will be for us to work together to restore our island home to normal," Dunkley said.  Loading weather data ...</text>
            <url>http://www.cnn.com/2014/10/17/world/americas/hurricane-gonzalo/index.html?hpt=ila_c1</url>
            <videos>
                <video>http://ht.cdn.turner.com/cnn/big/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn.smil</video>
                <video>http://cnnios-f.akamaihd.net/i/cnn/big/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_ios_,150,440,650,1240,.mp4.csmil/master.m3u8?__b__=650</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_155148_768x432_1300k.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_640x360_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_ios_150.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_cnn_iphone_cell.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_ios_audio.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_155148_640x360_900k.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn.ipad.qtref.mov</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_155148_1280x720_3500k.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_640x360_900k.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_cnn_iphone_wifi_hi.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_ios_1240.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_ios_440.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_320x180_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn.qtref.mov</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_ios_650.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_512x288_550k.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_384x216_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_155148_896x504_1850k.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_155148_512x288_550k.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_416x234_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_768x432_1300k.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_ios_3000.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_1280x720_3500k.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_ios_840.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_576x324_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_896x504_1850k.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_1280x720.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_768x432.mp4</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_256x144_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/tech/2014/09/11/pkg-build-tomorrow-hurricane-hunters-noaa-planes.cnn_youtube_640x360.flv</video>
            </videos>
        </news_item>
    </news_latinamerica>
    <news_middleeast>
        <news_item>
            <title>ISIS: Will it 'weaponize' foreign fighters? (Opinion) - CNN.com</title>
            <date>2014-10-16T20:08:48Z</date>
            <author>Thomas Hegghammer</author>
            <highlights>Likelihood of foreign fighters planning attacks in West varies by where they were, writer says ISIS less interested in planning attacks overseas than al Qaeda, Thomas Hegghammer says ISIS is unlikely to go all in on global operations the way al Qaeda has, he says</highlights>
            <text>Editor's note: Thomas Hegghammer is director of terrorism research at the Norwegian Defence Research Establishment and author of "Jihad in Saudi Arabia: Violence and Pan-Islamism since 1979." The views expressed are solely those of the author. (CNN) -- How big a threat do foreign fighters in Syria and Iraq pose to the West? It's a question that has been much on the mind of policymakers and commentators, especially since U.S. President Barack Obama announced the United States was ramping up its military role in the region. Will such fighters return with dangerous new skills and experience that they are determined to use against their home country? Or is the potential threat by these fighters overhyped? The answer depends on what the Islamic State of Iraq and Syria decides to do with them. So far, jihadi groups in Syria have not been sending foreign fighters on attack missions in the West in any sort of systematic way. But if the group decides to "weaponize" its fighters, we will have a much bigger problem on our hands. Since 2011, around 3,000 Western Muslims have gone to Syria, where many have joined the most radical elements of the insurgency. And there is no question that some of these individuals will pose a terrorist threat when they return. We know this because it has already happened -- Syria veterans are suspected of involvement in one successful and at least six unsuccessful alleged attacks in Europe and Australia over the past year. Yet there is no reason to expect all -- or even a majority -- of these people to try to attack us in the future. During my research, I have found that of all Western Muslims who joined conflict zones before 2011, no more than one in nine moved on to terrorism in the West. In fact, this estimate is probably at the high end -- the real historical average may be closer to one in 15 or 20. This suggests that the more helpful question is therefore not whether the foreign fighters in Syria are a threat, but what proportion of them will be. Can we not simply assume that somewhere between one in nine or one in 20 of the fighters in Syria will become terrorists, and try to plan accordingly? Unfortunately, it's not that simple because the "blowback rate" -- the proportion of outgoing fighters who later return to attack -- varies significantly between destinations. Take the conflict in Somalia, for example, which attracted hundreds of Western foreign fighters in the previous decade, but produced few attacking returnees. In contrast, of those who went to Afghanistan and Pakistan in the same period, a substantial proportion plotted attacks on their return. So, how can we determine whether Syria will produce foreign fighters that are more like Somalia or more like Afghanistan and Pakistan in terms of blowback? It largely depends on whether you have a group in the theater of conflict that strategically targets the West. For example, the Afghanistan-Pakistan area has a high blowback rate because it is home to the so-called al Qaeda Central, a group whose sole preoccupation is to mount attacks in the West. Al Qaeda excelled at taking foreign fighters who had come to fight with the Taliban and persuading them to undertake attacks in Europe or the United States instead. Most other jihadi groups, even al Qaeda's own affiliates, are not equally invested in this strategy. True, they all spout anti-American rhetoric and may even dabble in anti-Western extremist actions. But they invest the bulk of their resources in local operations. And so far, that has been true of ISIS, too. Of course, if you look for anti-Western statements and links to potential international plots, you will find them. But these indications actually make up a small proportion of the group's overall ideological production and military operations. The fact is that there is little to suggest that ISIS has had a sustained and centrally directed global operations program. This is one of the reasons why the blowback rate from Syria has so far been low, several plots notwithstanding. Six plots involving a total of, say, 10 or 20 Syria veterans make for a blowback rate of one in 150 or one in 300. Yes, it is still early in the conflict, and several plots may have gone unreported. But Syria is still looking like a low blowback foreign fighter destination. There is, however, the question of whether Western intervention in Iraq and Syria will cause ISIS to go global. Certainly, the group has taken a more anti-Western posture over the past few months. It has repeatedly threatened to attack the United States, and it has beheaded American hostages in Syria. In a noteworthy statement, for example, ISIS spokesman Abu Muhammad al-Adnani recently called on supporters worldwide to attack members of the coalition in any way possible. So we should not be surprised if ISIS embarks on a limited but sustained external operations effort, along the lines of al Qaeda in the Arabian Peninsula in Yemen, which combines a primarily local agenda with a small global side operation. Ultimately, though, ISIS is unlikely to go all in on global operations the way al Qaeda Central has. The organization is not designed for that, and such a strategy is not compatible with its state-building ambitions. Besides, ISIS' threats have so far differed in tone from those of al Qaeda Central. Where the latter says, in effect, that "we're coming at you regardless," ISIS has basically been saying, "We'll come at you if you attack us." It's a somewhat more reluctant declaration of war. None of this is to suggest that some foreign fighters in Syria won't come back and do bad things regardless of what ISIS' leaders choose to do -- they undoubtedly will. And it is also important to remember one more thing, namely that although the early signs suggest that the threat from foreign fighters returning is low, the potential for attacks is still there. Indeed, if ISIS starts to "weaponize" its Western recruits in a strategic way, then the foreign fighter threat will take on a more significant -- and more deadly -- complexion than it has so far. Read CNNOpinion's new Flipboard magazine. Follow us on Twitter @CNNOpinion. Join us on Facebook.com/CNNOpinion.  Loading weather data ...</text>
            <url>http://www.cnn.com/2014/10/16/opinion/hegghammer-isis-foreign-fighters/index.html?hpt=imi_t2</url>
            <photos>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141016115255-isis-kobani-1016-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141014151105-05-syria-1014-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141014151547-06-syria-1014-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141014084125-02-syria-1014-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141014084133-03-syria-1014-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141014084140-04-syria-1014-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141006124101-01-syria-unrest-1005-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141009182804-29-week-in-photos-1010-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141002074109-02-iraq-1002-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140929121700-01-iraq-0929-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141002175915-27-week-in-photos-1003-restricted-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140928162432-syria-0928-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141014122038-navy-missiles-isis-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140925182341-38-week-in-photos-0926-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140922124855-03-syrian-refugees-0922-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140922124802-02-syrian-refugees-0922-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140918165444-01-week-in-photos-0919-restricted-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140911171218-02-iraq-0911-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141014123540-kerry-iraq-0910-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140910075002-02-iraq-crisis-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140904071506-02-iraq-0904-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140901184024-iraq-0901-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140827164803-01-iraq-0827-restricted-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140827165139-02-iraq-0827-restricted-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140827165432-03-iraq-0827-restricted-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140821105714-01-iraq-0821-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140819085821-01-iraq-0819-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141014132319-iraq-airstrike-0818-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140814144755-01-iraq-0814-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140814144938-02-iraq-0814-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140813131741-03-iraq-0813-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140814173254-08-week-in-photos-0815-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141014125936-iraq-0809-restricted-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140807104933-01-iraq-0807-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140807105102-restricted-02-iraq-0807-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141014132656-iraq-0731-restricted-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141014130903-syria-0709-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/141014131619-iraq-0702-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140627080002-01-iraq-0627-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140627080752-06-iraq-0627-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140627080936-07-iraq-0627-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140619071843-01-iraq-0619-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140619072433-04-iraq-0619-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140618070823-01-iraq-0618-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140613113153-01-iraq-unrest-0613-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140613113159-02-iraq-unrest-0613-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140613113205-03-iraq-unrest-0613-restricted-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
                <photo>http://i2.cdn.turner.com/cnn/dam/assets/140612180850-27-week-in-photos-0612-horizontal-gallery.jpg</photo>
            </photos>
        </news_item>
        <news_item>
            <title>ISIS pushed back with help of U.S. airstrikes in Kobani - CNN.com</title>
            <date>2014-10-16T15:23:53Z</date>
            <author>Susanna Capelouto, CNN</author>
            <highlights>NEW: U.S. jets are increasing bombing of Kobani due to heavier ISIS presence NEW: Pentagon says that doesn't mean U.S. strategy is shifting on the city's value 14 U.S. airstrikes on ISIS positions in Kobani help Kurdish fighters turn the tide, activist says ISIS gaining ground in Iraq's Anbar province, local official says</highlights>
            <text>(CNN) -- The increased number of U.S. airstrikes against ISIS in the Syrian city of Kobani reflects more targets of opportunity, not a change in the campaign against the vicious Islamist group, a Pentagon spokesman said Thursday. The strikes are helping Kurdish fighters on the ground push back ISIS militants in the Syrian town, according to sources there. "There's been no strategic shift here, as far as I know, at least from the military perspective, about Kobani or any other town," Rear Adm. John Kirby said, making a unique appearance at the State Department's daily briefing. In recent weeks, administration and U.S. defense officials have said it wasn't essential to keep the city, not far from the border with Turkey, from becoming the latest in Syria to fall into ISIS hands. "We never said Kobani didn't matter," Kirby said. "What makes Kobani matter for us from an airstrike perspective is that (ISIS is) there, and that they want it." Kirby said the number of airstrikes in Syria or Iraq depends on how "target rich" an area is. The past few days around Kobani have seen more ISIS targets, he said. There are more ISIS fights there with more force, Kirby said. U.S. fighter jets conducted at least 14 raids near Kobani on Wednesday and Thursday, according to U.S. Central Command. Initial reports show the strikes hit 19 ISIS buildings and 10 other targets, including command posts, sniper positions and a staging location, the U.S. military said. According to CNN's math, that makes 122 strikes on the city, most of any town in what the military recently labeled Operation Inherent Resolve. Street by street The battle for Kobani has become a street fight over control of hills and neighborhoods and witnessed by TV cameras pointed there from Turkey. These strikes on small targets in Kobani, such as sniper positions, are "tactical" in nature -- without the widespread "strategic" affect against ISIS that U.S. officials have said is the foundation for the U.S. operation in Syria, a senior U.S. military official told CNN's Barbara Starr. "It's not 'whack-a-mole,' " Kirby said. "The idea isn't to just put a warhead on a forehead every single day. The idea is to try to get at their ability to sustain themselves and to disrupt their strategy." One Kurdish fighter told CNN Thursday that ISIS has been forced from many parts of the city, but still controls some key buildings including the hospital and the important Asayish building in the middle of Kobani, which served as headquarters for the Kurdish People's Protection Units, or YPG. Kurdish forces have control of the southwest entrance of the city and have taken some buildings back from ISIS fighters in one neighborhood, next to the heavily contested eastern industrial area of the city. The airstrikes over the past few days have helped Kurdish YPG fighters turn into an offensive rather than a defensive force, one activist said. But, he adds, "there is still street fighting in the east and in the south" of Kobani. "This is an infantry battle now and traditional reconnaissance does not work," said Anthony Cordesman with the Center for Strategic and International Studies. It's hard to get correct information, making the results of the airstrikes indecisive, he said. A U.S. Defense officials told CNN that good weather played a role in the Kobani airstrikes, because the targets were readily located by overhead surveillance. In Iraq on the other hand, bad weather has forced a slowdown in strikes, the official said. Joint Chiefs chairman: 'I don't see' Baghdad falling ISIS pushing ahead in Iraq? Militants have tightened their grip over an area about 15 miles south of Fallujah, an Anbar province official said Thursday. ISIS has brought many of its fighters, armed with heavy weaponry and machinery, in order to attack and control the town of Amiryat al-Falluja, the head of the town's council, Shaker Mahmoud, said Thusday. Mahmoud urged the Iraqi government to send military reinforcements to support the security forces inside the town. Obama on ISIS: Expect 'long-term campaign' ISIS advances have slowed and the group has changed formation, communication and tactics making them "harder to hit," Kirby said. He called for "strategic patience" in measuring the success of the operation. Militants continue to surround a major airbase in the Iraq's Anbar province and U.S. officials say they're continuing airstrikes there to help Iraqi forces. "In Anbar province, our hope is to stop or halt that tactical initiative and momentum that they (ISIS) have," Gen. John Allen, the special presidential envoy on ISIS, said Wednesday. It is clear that ISIS "has made substantial gains in Iraq," he said. A senior U.S. military official told CNN the fight in Anbar is "very tough," but "Iraqi forces are holding their own in some places." U.S. officials do not see the Ein Al-Assad military base in Anbar on the verge of being overrun by ISIS, the official said. Opinion: Why we must talk to the bad guys --- even ISIS ISIS car bomb in Baghdad At least five people were killed and 15 were injured when two car bombs exploded in the al-Hurriya Shiite neighborhood in Baghdad Thursday, according to police. At least two people died when another car bomb exploded at a security checkpoint near al-Talbiya Bridge in eastern Baghdad. ISIS released a statement claiming responsibility for the bombings. CNN's Ingrid Formanek, Hamdi Alkhshali and Kareem Khadder contributed to this story Loading weather data ...</text>
            <url>http://www.cnn.com/2014/10/16/world/meast/isis-threat/index.html?hpt=imi_c1</url>
            <videos>
                <video>http://ht.cdn.turner.com/cnn/big/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn.smil</video>
                <video>http://cnnios-f.akamaihd.net/i/cnn/big/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_ios_,150,440,650,1240,.mp4.csmil/master.m3u8?__b__=650</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_211147_768x432_1300k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_ios_150.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_640x360_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_cnn_iphone_cell.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_ios_audio.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_211147_640x360_900k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn.ipad.qtref.mov</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_211147_1280x720_3500k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_640x360_900k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_cnn_iphone_wifi_hi.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_ios_1240.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_ios_440.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn.qtref.mov</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_320x180_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_ios_650.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_512x288_550k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_384x216_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn.scc</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_211147_896x504_1850k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_211147_512x288_550k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_416x234_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_768x432_1300k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_ios_3000.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_ios_840.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_1280x720_3500k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_576x324_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_896x504_1850k.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_1280x720.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_768x432.mp4</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_256x144_dl.flv</video>
                <video>/world/2014/10/16/lead-dnt-sciutto-isis-kobani-syria.cnn_youtube_640x360.flv</video>
            </videos>
        </news_item>
    </news_middleeast>
</cnn_news_list>